{
  "cards": [
    { "front": "a, an", "back": "um, uma", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "ability", "back": "habilidade", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "about", "back": "sobre", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "above", "back": "acima", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "abroad", "back": "no exterior", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "absolute", "back": "absoluto", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "absolutely", "back": "absolutamente", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "academic", "back": "acadêmico", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "accept", "back": "aceitar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "acceptable", "back": "aceitável", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "access", "back": "acesso", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "accident", "back": "acidente", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "accompany", "back": "acompanhar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "according", "back": "segundo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "account", "back": "conta", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "accurate", "back": "preciso", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "accuse", "back": "acusar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "ache", "back": "dor", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "achieve", "back": "alcançar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "achievement", "back": "conquista", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "acknowledge", "back": "reconhecer", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "acquire", "back": "adquirir", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "across", "back": "através", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "act", "back": "agir", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "action", "back": "ação", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "active", "back": "ativo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "activity", "back": "atividade", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "actor", "back": "ator", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "actress", "back": "atriz", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "actual", "back": "atual", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "actually", "back": "realmente", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "adapt", "back": "adaptar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "add", "back": "adicionar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "addition", "back": "adição", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "additional", "back": "adicional", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "address", "back": "endereço", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    {
      "front": "administration",
      "back": "administração",
      "tags": ["vocabulary"]
    },
    { "front": "admire", "back": "admirar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "admit", "back": "admitir", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "adopt", "back": "adotar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "advance", "back": "avançar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "advanced", "back": "avançado", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "advantage", "back": "vantagem", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "adventure", "back": "aventura", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "advertise", "back": "anunciar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "advertisement", "back": "anúncio", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "advertising", "back": "publicidade", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "advice", "back": "conselho", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "advise", "back": "aconselhar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "affair", "back": "caso", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "affect", "back": "afetar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "afford", "back": "permitir-se", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "afraid", "back": "com medo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "after", "back": "depois", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "afternoon", "back": "tarde", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "afterward", "back": "depois", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "again", "back": "novamente", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "against", "back": "contra", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "age", "back": "idade", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "agency", "back": "agência", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "agenda", "back": "agenda", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "agent", "back": "agente", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "aggressive", "back": "agressivo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "ago", "back": "atrás", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "agree", "back": "concordar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "agreement", "back": "acordo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "ah", "back": "ah", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "ahead", "back": "à frente", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "aid", "back": "ajuda", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "aim", "back": "objetivo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "air", "back": "ar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "aircraft", "back": "aeronave", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "airline", "back": "companhia aérea", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "airport", "back": "aeroporto", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "alarm", "back": "alarme", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "album", "back": "álbum", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "alcohol", "back": "álcool", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "alcoholic", "back": "alcoólico", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "alive", "back": "vivo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "all", "back": "tudo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "allow", "back": "permitir", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "almost", "back": "quase", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "alone", "back": "sozinho", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "along", "back": "ao longo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "already", "back": "já", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "also", "back": "também", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "alter", "back": "alterar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "alternative", "back": "alternativa", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "although", "back": "embora", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "always", "back": "sempre", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "amazed", "back": "impressionado", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "amazing", "back": "incrível", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "ambition", "back": "ambição", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "among", "back": "entre", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "amount", "back": "quantidade", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "analysis", "back": "análise", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "analyze", "back": "analisar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "ancient", "back": "antigo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "and", "back": "e", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "anger", "back": "raiva", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "angle", "back": "ângulo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "angry", "back": "zangado", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "animal", "back": "animal", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "ankle", "back": "tornozelo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "anniversary", "back": "aniversário", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "announce", "back": "anunciar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "announcement", "back": "anúncio", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "annoy", "back": "irritar", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "annoyed", "back": "irritado", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "annoying", "back": "irritante", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "annual", "back": "anual", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "another", "back": "outro", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "answer", "back": "resposta", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "anxious", "back": "ansioso", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "any", "back": "qualquer", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "anybody", "back": "alguém", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "anymore", "back": "mais", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "anyone", "back": "qualquer um", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "anything", "back": "qualquer coisa", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    {
      "front": "anywhere",
      "back": "em qualquer lugar",
      "tags": ["vocabulary"]
    },
    { "front": "apart", "back": "separado", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "apartment", "back": "apartamento", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "apologize", "back": "pedir desculpas", "tags": ["vocabulary"] },
    { "front": "app", "back": "aplicativo", "tags": ["vocabulary"] }
  ]
}
